## PRODUCT MANAGER & ACCOUNTS MANAGER

Summary

Human Resources Administration professional who has a comprehensive understanding of labor laws and benefits administration. Exceptional ability to manage external and internal communication protocol while being proficient with budget requirements and deadlines. Highly effective at incorporating creative leadership and management skills to achieve overall business objectives. Expertise in: HR Focus Office Administration Creative Skill Employee Relations Client Database Management Web Design Training & Recruiting Quickbooks Enterprise Graphic Design Hiring & Retention Invoicing & Accounts Payable CAD/Solidworks Compensation & Payroll Marketing - Email, SEO, Analytics Adobe Creative Suite Regulation Compliance Inventory Management Tradeshow Design Personnel Record Maintenance Sales & Social Media Marketing Printmaking Highlights

Additional Skills: Adobe Creative Suite- Illustrator; Photoshop; InDesign; Bridge; DreamWeaver Web Design & HTML Creative Print/Digital Media

Experience

Product Manager & Accounts Manager

April 2013 to May 2015 National Financial Partners Corp. il/4 Westerville, OH

- Provided employee training on a new product brand while conducting orientations to teach to outside clients.
- Introduced and implemented new organizational practices for inter-office use between two existing company branches both in Philadelphia and Washington D.C.
- Managed and marketed sales and product information for a product line of 300+ products.
- Travelled 8-10 times a year to promote company objectives and product information to national clients via tradeshows and conferences.
- Facilitated all tradeshow efforts including: booth design, website promotion, brochure & mailers, and setup/dismantling of all show materials.
   Key improvements: -Met with all new hires for procedure/training, benefits, and implementation of sales practices -Developed new organizational protocol to combat and improve overall office communication -Improved paperwork processing time by 50% to streamline client contact and direct sales -Helped foster a positive environment by serving as a link between staff and management -Established product line and built a client database from scratch -Improved sales each quarter by 25-30% each quarter during my tenure

## Marketing Manager & Graphic Designer

February 2012 to April 2013 Metaphase Technologies i1/4 City, STATE

- Maintained a business website with over 200 individual products.
- Used HTML and built-in site manager to create dedicated product pages
- Graphic & Web design for product announcements and industry matched search engines
- First point of contact for all marketing and promotion leads for company presence
- Scheduled and managed multiple tradeshows in Boston, Chicago, and Stuttgart Germany. Key improvements: -Redesigned a broken site
  into a respectable company website with updated HTML and SEO tags -Developed a database of all CAD, STEP, & DXF product files
  and made them easily available on site -Created a more refined logo and recognizable theme to the Metaphase Brand -Acquired new
  customers through marketing partnerships with outside leading industry sites -Improved overall website traffic by 20% within the first month
  and kept it at a steady incline

## Office Operations Manager

October 2011 to February 2012 Superior Glass And Mirror it/4 City, STATE In charge of customer relations and accounts for commercial and storefront glass installation jobs. Managed schedules for three teams of technicians to efficiently complete jobs each week. First point of contact for all new and continuing accounts and in charge of maintaining relations with those accounts. Effectively acquired and serviced new clients while directly working with vendors and suppliers for customer satisfaction. Key improvements: -Developed numerous documents to make scheduling, invoicing, and new job leads more efficient -Invoiced and received on accounts lowering the number of open accounts overall -Created a more refined calendar for three teams of workers, served as dispatcher -Acquired new customers through referrals and leads by consistent customer interaction

Education

Bachelor of Science: Journalism, Advertising/Integrated Marketing Communications Southern Illinois University Carbondale Bachelor of Science, Southern Illinois University Carbondale (SIUC), May 2011 Major: Journalism: Specialization: Advertising/Integrated Marketing Communications Minors in Psychology & Art and Design

Affiliations

PA SPCA - Animal Handler & Volunteer

Presentations

Travelled 8-10 times a year to promote company objectives and product information to national clients via tradeshows and conferences Skills

Database, Tradeshows, Clients, Accounts Manager, Benefits, Booth, Direct Sales, New Hires, Of Sales, Product Manager, Sales, Sales And, Tradeshow, Training, Leads, Marketing, Auto Cad, Cad, Engines, Html, Metaphase, Search Engine Optimization, Seo, Web Design, Accounts Payable, Benefits Administration, Budget, Communication Protocol, Compensation, Database Management, Digital Media, Dreamweaver, Employee Relations, Graphic Design, Hr, Human Resources, Illustration, Illustrator, Indesign, Inventory, Labor Laws, Maintenance, Office Administration, Payroll, Photoshop, Quickbooks, Recruiting, Social Media Marketing, Solidworks, Accounts And, Accounts For, Customer Interaction, Customer Relations, Dispatcher, Invoicing, Operations, Operations Manager, Satisfaction, Scheduling, Advertising, Marketing Communications